freeofferstoday.in 2015-06-30

# Privacy Policy - FreeOffersToday.in

**Privacy Policy**

The policies below are applicable to freeofferstoday.in.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

freeofferstoday respects each individual user’s right to privacy. freeofferstoday does not collect personal identifying information unless such information is specifically and knowingly provided from users during contests, surveys, sweepstakes, site registration, or use of public areas, such as a forum. From time to time, we share aggregated site traffic information with our partners and advertisers. This data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Information You Give Us:**

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information you provide for such purposes as responding to your interactions with our site, customizing our site for you, improving our site, working with merchants to resolve your complaints and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information:**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses dealnews.com or one of the other Web sites we produce.

**Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms**

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Third Party Offers or Mailing Lists**

Users that have subscribed to freeofferstoday newsletters or email alerts will occasionally receive special announcement emails including updates about changes and improvements to the freeofferstoday site, announcements about exclusive giveaways and promotions as well as information on products, services or special deals (our’s or a third party’s). Out of respect for the privacy of our users, these types of communications will only come from freeofferstoday (as we will never sell your email address) and there will always be the option to “opt-out” of these special announcement emails.

**Choice: Opt-In and Opt-Out**

Our users are given the opportunity to “opt-in” to having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. freeofferstoday does not supply identifying information to other companies, or use such information for its own purposes including but not limited to email newsletters, unless the user “opts-in” for such purposes by specifically allowing usage. (Identifying information must necessarily be used when notifying a user of requested information, such as email used for the alerts function, and notification the outcome of an entry in a contest, survey or sweepstakes.)

Once subscribed, users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of (i.e., discontinue receiving) these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or contact us via [this online contact form](http://www.freeofferstoday.in/contact-us/). We also offer opt-out mechanisms in the text of each email we send, and the user may contact us at the street address at the top of this page to opt-out.

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information.

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or a legal process served on our Web site.

On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, although they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Security**

freeofferstoday uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. However, freeofferstoday is not responsible for any breach of security. If a freeofferstoday user knowingly provides personal information, such as a name or email address, in a forum or other public service, that user should be aware that the information provided can be collected and used by third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of freeofferstoday. However, at registration a user can choose whether an email is disclosed in the profile/post of the forum user.

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. freeofferstoday will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. freeofferstoday stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

**Cookies**

Non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of freeofferstoday’ Internet servers (i.e. log file information like IP address) or through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that our site places on your computer’s hard drive to recognize repeat users and facilitate the user’s use of the site. Also, our cookies allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data for content improvement, targeted advertising, and marketing and promotional purposes.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). Users should be aware that freeofferstoday cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or other third parties. Most browsers allow a user to deny cookies; however, users should note that cookies may be required to provide certain web site features.

**Third Party Advertising**

Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by LinkShare, Commision Junction, Performics, and our other Web advertising partners. These third party advertising partners collect information about users’ visits to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), and use that information to serve ads to users on this site, other websites, and other forms of media. For more information about LinkShare, Commission Junction, Performics, cookies, and how to “opt-out Please understand that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

**ATTENTION KIDS**

ATTENTION KIDS: No information should be submitted to freeofferstoday by children under 18 years of age without their parent’s or guardian’s consent. freeofferstoday does not monitor the age of its user audience.

freeofferstoday reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting notice of the existence of a new privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
